Guide to the Beer Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- ALICE BALDWIN BEER, 1896-1969; Series IV; 8.5' (21 boxes)
  - Antique Textiles Business
    - Correspondence with Clients and Dealers
      - Costantino, Ruth Teschner, 1932-1935 (Box 129, Folder 95)
      - Cummin, Mrs. Gaylord, 1942-1943 (Box 129, Folder 96)
      - De Spiridon, Anna, 1942-1944 (Box 129, Folder 97)
      - Drinker, Mrs. James B., and Nell, Mrs. Katherine: correspondence re: sale of Drinker collection, 1941-1944 (Box 129, Folder 98)
      - DuPont, H. F., 1939-1944 (Box 129, Folder 99)
      - Gamble, Elisabeth C., 1933-1938, 1939-1937, 1939-1942 (Box 129, Folder 100-103)
      - Beer v. Godart; correspondence with Benedict Ginsherg (attorney), 1933-1934 (Box 130, Folder 104)
      - Healey, Sumner, 1937-1944 (Box 130, Folder 105)
      - Hutaff, John, 1939-1944 (Box 130, Folder 106)
      - Hutcheson, Mrs. William, 1941-1944 (Box 130, Folder 107)
      - Lewisohn, Irene, 1934-1944 (Box 130, Folder 109)
      - McCauslan, Dorothy, 1932-1937 (Box 130, Folder 110)
      - McMullen, J. B, 1938-1942 (Box 130, Folder 111)
      - Moore, Roland, 1940-1944 (Box 130, Folder 112)
      - Old English Galleries, 1932-1935 (Box 130, Folder 113)
      - Pleadwell, Amy: correspondence and lists of stock, 1934-1942 (Box 130, Folder 114)
      - Pleadwell, Amy: records of stock returned or sold, 1938-1942 (Box 130, Folder 115)
      - Pleadwell, Amy, 1943-1944 (Box 130, Folder 116)
      - Riefstahl textile collection: correspondence, notes re: sale, 1937-1944 (Box 131, Folder 117)
      - Robeson, Katharine M., 1935-1938 (Box 131, Folder 118-119)
      - Sabbagh, Cesar, 1936-1937 (Box 131, Folder 120)
      - Scalamandre, Franco, 1934-1941 (Box 131, Folder 121)
      - Schernikow, Margaret, 1929-1932 (Box 131, Folder 122)
      - Sherman, Mrs. Frederick W., 1942-1944 (Box 131, Folder 123)
      - Snow, Julia D. S., 1940-1941 (Box 131, Folder 124)
      - Spanish embroidery and lace collection; correspondence With J. A. Weissherger, 1929, 1932-1938 (Box 131, Folder 125)
      - Spanish embroidery and lace collection; correspondence with museums and individuals, 1932-1939 (Box 131, Folder 126)
      - Spanish embroidery and lace collection; lists, notes, photographs, shipment and insurance, 1932 (Box 131, Folder 127)
      - Stratford Hall (Virginia) Restoration; correspondence with Mrs. Gaylord Cummin, 1940 (Box 131, Folder 128)
      - Stratford Hall Restoration: correspondence with Mrs. Gaylord Cummin, 1941 (Box 131, Folder 129)
      - Stratford Hall Restoration: notes, samples relating to correspondence with Mrs. Gaylord Cummin, 1940-1941 (Box 132, Folder 130)
      - Stratford Hall Restoration: correspondence with Mrs. Maurice Brix, 1940 (Box 132, Folder 131)
      - correspondence with Mrs. Mason Garfield and Mrs. Breckenridge Long, 1940 (Box 132, Folder 131)
      - Stratford Hall Restoration: correspondence with Edward Maag, 1940 (Box 132, Folder 132)
      - Stratford Hall Restoration: correspondence with dealers, notes, on securing materials, 1940 (Box 132, Folder 133)
      - Sullivan (Mary) Estate, 1939-1944 (Box 132, Folder 134)
      - Taylor, Elia, 1930-1935 (Box 132, Folder 135-136)
      - Trent House; materials, 1939 (Box 132, Folder 137)
      - Ullman, Lillian, 1940-1941 (Box 132, Folder 138)
      - Walker, Sybil, 1934-1937 (Box 132, Folder 139)
      - Weissberger, Herbert P. and Demotte, Inc., 1935-1944 (Box 132, Folder 140)
      - Weissberger, José A, and Baron Cassel van Down, 1941-1944 (Box 132, Folder 141)
      - Wilkins, Frederic F., 1930-1936 (Box 132, Folder 142)
      - Wood, Ruby Ross, 1936-1944 (Box 132, Folder 143)
      - Woodville & Company, 1932-1937 (Box 132, Folder 144)
      - Woolley, Edgar M., 1942-1943 (Box 132, Folder 145)
      - Woolley, Edgar M.: measurements and estimates, 1942-1943 (Box 133, Folder 146)
      - Woolley, Edgar M.: measurements plans and notes, 1942-1943 (Box 133, Folder 147)
      - Woolley, Edgar M.: work orders, 1942-1943 (Box 133, Folder 148)
      - Woolley, Edgar M.: materials ordered, 1942-1943 (Box 133, Folder 149)
      - Woolley, Edgar M.: materials paid for, 1942-1943 (Box 133, Folder 150)
      - Woolley, Edgar M.: bills and statements of expenditures, 1942-1943 (Box 133, Folder 151)
      - Woolley, Edgar M.: samples of materials and wallpaper (with notes) for bedrooms, 1943 (Box 133, Folder 152)
      - Woolley, Edgar M; samples of materials and wallpaper (with notes) in E, M. W.'s bedroom and sitting room, 1943 (Box 133, Folder 153)
      - Woolley, Edgar M; samples of materials and wallpaper (with notes) in parlors and library, 1943 (Box 133, Folder 154)
      - Wright, Anne, 1943-1944 (Box 133, Folder 155)
      - correspondence with museums: A-B, 1929-1944 (Box 133, Folder 156)
      - The Brooklyn Museum (John Graham), 1940-1942 (Box 134, Folder 157)
      - correspondence with museums: C-G, 1929-1944 (Box 134, Folder 158)
      - correspondence with museums: H-L, 1929-1944 (Box 134, Folder 159)
      - correspondence with museums: M-O, 1929-1944 (Box 134, Folder 160)
      - correspondence with museums: P-Z, 1929-1944 (Box 134, Folder 161)
      - correspondence about exhibits, 1934-1943, undated (Box 134, Folder 162-163)
    - Financial Records
      - accounts payable to consignors, 1938-1944 (Box 134, Folder 164)
      - bills paid, 1936-1937 (Box 134, Folder 165-166)
      - bills paid (1), 1938 (Box 135, Folder 167)
      - bills paid (2), 1938 (Box 135, Folder 168)
      - bills paid (1), 1939 (Box 135, Folder 169)
      - bills paid (2), 1939 (Box 135, Folder 170)
      - bills paid, 1940-1944 (Box 135, Folder 171-175)
      - rental bills, 1940-1944 (Box 135, Folder 176-177)
      - utilities bills, 1940-1944 (Box 135, Folder 178)
      - insurance policies on antique textiles, 1934-1937 (Box 136, Folder 179)
      - leases, 1941-1943 (Box 136, Folder 180)
      - loan payments, 1934-1936 (Box 136, Folder 181)
      - sales receipts, 1934-1935, 1937-1939 (Box 136, Folder 182-186)
      - sales receipts (1), 1940 (Box 136, Folder 187)
      - sales receipts (2), 1940 (Box 136, Folder 188)
      - sales receipts (3), 1940 (Box 136, Folder 189)
      - sales receipts (1), 1941 (Box 137, Folder 190)
      - sales receipts (2), 1941 (Box 137, Folder 191)
      - sales receipts, 1942 (Box 137, Folder 192)
      - Christmas lists (for gifts in office building), 1937-1943 (Box 137, Folder 193)
    - Stock Inventories
      - old consignments, 1932-1940 (Box 137, Folder 194)
      - stock returned to consignors (1), 1934-1937 (Box 137, Folder 195)
      - stock returned to consignors (2), 1934-1937 (Box 137, Folder 196)
      - stock returned to consignors (1), 1938-1940 (Box 137, Folder 197)
      - stock returned to consignors (2), 1938-1940 (Box 137, Folder 198)
      - stock returned to consignors (3), 1938-1940 (Box 138, Folder 199)
      - stock returned to consignors (1), 1941 (Box 138, Folder 200)
      - stock returned to consignors (2), 1941 (Box 138, Folder 201)
      - stock returned to consignors, 1942 (Box 138, Folder 202)
      - stock returned to consignors (1), 1944 May (Box 138, Folder 203)
      - stock returned to consignors (2), 1944 May (Box 138, Folder 204)
      - stock returned from temporary consignment to consignors (1), 1937-1939 (Box 138, Folder 205)
      - stock returned from temporary consignment to consignors (2), 1937-1939 (Box 138, Folder 206)
      - stock of other consignors returned (1), 1944 (Box 138, Folder 207)
      - stock of other consignors returned (2), 1944 (Box 139, Folder 208)
      - stock of other consignors returned (3), 1944 (Box 139, Folder 209)
      - stock returned from memo, 1933-1939 (Box 139, Folder 210)
      - stock returned from memo (1), 1940-1942 (Box 139, Folder 211)
      - stock returned from memo (2), 1940-1942 (Box 139, Folder 212)
      - stock returned from memo (1), 1943 (Box 139, Folder 213)
      - stock returned from memo (2), 1943 (Box 139, Folder 214)
      - stock returned from memo, 1944 (Box 139, Folder 215)
      - stock returned from memo or consignment, 1943 (Box 140, Folder 216)
      - samples of modern stock returned (receipts), 1938, 1940-1942 (Box 140, Folder 217-218)
      - samples of modern stock returned (receipts), 1943-1944 (Box 140, Folder 218)
      - stock records, 1943-1944 (Box 140, Folder 219)
    - Reference Material
      - bibliographies, notes, outlines (1), undated (Box 140, Folder 220)
      - bibliographies, notes, outlines (2), undated (Box 140, Folder 221)
      - clippings, catalogues, undated (Box 140, Folder 222)
      - conference on materials used in American homes, 1942 April 18 (Box 140, Folder 223)
      - designs for cards made by Doris Riker Beer from a Spanish embroidery, undated (Box 140, Folder 224)
      - European buying trips: notebooks, 1928-1936 (Box 141, Folder 225-226)
      - European buying trips: notes, bills, lists of purchases, 1928-1929 (Box 141, Folder 227)
      - European buying trips: bills and receipts from Spain, 1928-1929 (Box 141, Folder 228)
      - European buying trips: notebook on purchases, 1930 (Box 141, Folder 229)
      - European buying trips: addresses and notes on dealers (primarily business cards), Circa 1930 (Box 141, Folder 230)
      - European buying trips: miscellaneous notes, 1930 (Box 141, Folder 231)
      - European buying trips: Paris addresses, notes, 1930-1931 (Box 141, Folder 232)
      - European buying trips: record of purchases, 1931 (Box 141, Folder 233)
      - European buying trips: correspondence, 1931, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 234)
      - European buying trips: lists of purchases, bills, receipts, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 235)
      - European buying trips: shipments of goods, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 236)
      - European buying trips: purchase and shipments of goods, 1937 (Box 141, Folder 237)
      - European buying trips: Casa Gustavo Guggenbuhl, 1939-1940 (Box 142, Folder 238)
      - historic houses, undated (Box 142, Folder 239)
      - Hunt collection or embroideries: description, 1941 (Box 142, Folder 240)
      - mailing lists and letters used for publicity, 1935-1938 (Box 142, Folder 241)
      - notes on lectures, 1929-1933 (Box 142, Folder 242-243)
      - photographs of textiles in stock, undated (Box 142, Folder 244)
      - photographs of textiles sold, undated (Box 142, Folder 245)
      - photographs of furniture and ornaments in stock, undated (Box 143, Folder 246)
      - photographs of furniture and ornaments sold, undated (Box 143, Folder 247)
      - photographs of a group of textiles and furniture, undated (Box 143, Folder 248)
      - photographic plates, undated (Box 143, Folder 249)
      - negatives of photographs of textiles and furniture, undated (Box 143, Folder 250)
      - research on textiles in stock and other notes, undated (Box 143, Folder 251)
      - toiles - names and dates of pieces, undated (Box 143, Folder 252)
      - miscellaneous textile samples and tickets, undated (Box 143, Folder 253)
    - Personal Files
      - certificates and membership cards, 1902-1964 (Box 144, Folder 254)
      - Columbus, Ohio Centenary Celebration: pageant., 1919 (Box 144, Folder 255)
        See also: box 127, folder 68
      - European trip: diary, 1911 (Box 144, Folder 256)
      - European trip: memorabilia, 1911 (Box 144, Folder 257)
      - European trip: travel notes., 1928 (Box 144, Folder 258)
        See also: box 141, folder 225-226
      - European trip; travel notes, 1931 (Box 144, Folder 259)
      - European trip: memorabilia, 1936 (Box 144, Folder 260)
      - European trip: travel notes, undated (Box 144, Folder 261)
      - folk songs, undated (Box 144, Folder 262)
      - juvenilia: compositions and drawings, 1897-1898, undated (Box 144, Folder 263)
      - Neighborhood Playhouse, The programs, reviews, 1922-1923 (Box 144, Folder 264)
        See also: boxes 125-128, folders 1-80
      - notes on current events, 1909 (Box 144, Folder 265)
      - Vassar College: commencement, 1910 (Box 144, Folder 266)
      - Vassar College: memorabilia, 1906-1910 (Box 145, Folder 267)
      - Vassar College: memorabilia, 1906-1910 (Box 145, Folder 268)
      - memorabilia: miscellaneous, 1911-1938, undated (Box 145, Folder 269)
      - small pillow with Gibson girl design, presumably made by Alice Baldwin Beer (Box 145, Folder 269A)
      - biographical information, Undated, 1978 (Box 145, Folder 270)
- RICHARD CAMERON BEER, 1901-1959; Series V; 1.5' (4 boxes)
  Correspondence is arranged chronologically. Correspondence concerning publication of his writings and letters from readers are filed after the general chronological sequence.
  Published Writings is arranged chronologically.
  Unpublished Writings is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Correspondence
    - 1911-1958 (Box 146, Folder 1-2)
    - correspondence about publication; A-Z, 1951-1958 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - correspondence about publication: McIntosh and Otis, Inc., 1954-1959, undated (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - correspondence about publication: correspondence with Austin (Mary) Strong and Edward West about "The Unpredictable Austin Strong," Yankee 1956 Mar, 1952-1958, undated (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - correspondence about publication: Yankee, 1955-1959 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - letters from readers, 1955-[1959?] (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - letters from men profiled in The Art News, Circa 1933-1934 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Published Writings
    - "Timothy J.," Saturday Evening Post, 1919 June 21 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - "Cured of an Awful Secret," Liberty, 1927 December 24 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - The Art News series, 1933 May-1934 February 17, 1934 February 24-May (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - The Art News series; notes and background material, Circa (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - "Gulls, Mountains, and Henry Smith," Country Life, 1934 August (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - "Moustache Cups," Country Life, 1934 November (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - "Wanted: An American School of Art," and "The Eagle's Nest," Country Life, 1935 April (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - "Yachts on Science Bent," Country Life, 1935 July (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - "The Wave that Drowned a Baby", 1951 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - "Elegy of an Island," Yankee, 1955 April (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - "The Unpredictable Austin Strong," Yankee, 1956 March (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - "Nine Niles of Railroad," Yankee, 1956 July (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - "'Sconset's Broadway Heyday," Yankee, 1957 June (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - "Early on Old North Wharf," The Inquirer and Mirror, 1958 August 15 (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - "Gold is Where You Find It," The Inquirer and Mirror, 1958 December 26 (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - "Footnote to History," The Inquirer and Mirror, Circa 1958-1959 (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - "Whale Oil Gus," Yankee: notes, drafts and printed version, 1959 July (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - "Whale Oil Gus," Yankee: correspondence, photographs and clippings used for background material, 1959 July (Box 147, Folder 27)
  - Unpublished Writings
    - "A Simple House in the Country", 1955 (Box 147, Folder 28)
    - "Afternoon of a Stentor" (or "Matinee"), undated (Box 147, Folder 29a)
    - "All About the House" (or "Strategy"), undated (Box 147, Folder 29b)
    - "The Contrition of Minnie", 1954 (Box 147, Folder 30)
    - "David and the Terrible Tiger", undated (Box 147, Folder 31)
    - "The 'Golden' Age" (or "Nephreticum and Co."), 1957 June (Box 147, Folder 32)
    - "Happy Birthday" (or "Palm Beach Calling"), 1953-1954 (Box 147, Folder 33)
    - "The Little Brown Pooch", undated (Box 147, Folder 34)
    - "The Little Wind and the Mystery of Old Man Olus", 1956 (Box 147, Folder 35)
    - "Lost American Lines" (poem), undated (Box 147, Folder 36)
    - "Luck", 1948 (Box 147, Folder 37)
    - "Monument to a Clown" (or "Marcelline"), 1955 (Box 147, Folder 38)
    - "Oh, Believe Me", 1954 (Box 147, Folder 39)
    - "The O'Henry Finish", 1954 (Box 147, Folder 40)
    - ["On Behalf of Mr. Bobbly"?], undated (Box 147, Folder 41)
    - "The Palace of Dim Night", undated (Box 147, Folder 42)
    - "The Privilege", undated (Box 147, Folder 43)
    - "The Story of Lamb", Circa 1953 (Box 147, Folder 44)
    - "There Are No Racoons on Nantucket", undated (Box 148, Folder 45)
    - "Tragedy", undated (Box 148, Folder 47)
    - "The Vindication of King", [1956?] (Box 148, Folder 48)
    - untitled story about Andrew Brier and his English wife, undated (Box 148, Folder 49)
    - untitled story about Henry Morgan or Henry Morgan Chadwick, also referred to as "The Bow of Arany", Circa 1949-1956 (Box 148, Folder 50)
    - untitled story set in Cuba, undated (Box 148, Folder 51)
    - notes and drafts for article on the Eastern Shore of Maryland for Country Life (with J. D. Tilghman), undated (Box 148, Folder 52)
    - notes and drafts for a story about a trip to Nantucket, 1959 spring (Box 148, Folder 53)
    - research notes on Nantucket documents, 1954 October 30 (Box 148, Folder 54)
    - miscellaneous research notes and incomplete drafts, undated (Box 148, Folder 55)
    - clippings about articles, 1917, 1936 (Box 148, Folder 56)
  - Personal Files
    - address book, undated (Box 148, Folder 57)
    - certificates, 1904-1908, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 58)
    - diplomatic credentials, 1917-1924 (Box 148, Folder 59)
    - Halsted School memorabilia, 1906, undated (Box 148, Folder 60)
    - juvenilia: school work, 1901, 1904 (Box 148, Folder 61)
    - Mackenzie School yearbook, Olim, 1909 (Box 148, Folder 62)
    - Mackenzie School yearbook, Olim, 1910 (Box 149, Folder 63)
    - phrenological character analysis, 1907 May 24 (Box 149, Folder 64)
    - scrapbook from consular years, Circa 1920-1925 (Box 149, Folder 65)
    - memorabilia, undated (Box 149, Folder 66)
    - biographical information, undated (Box 149, Folder 67)
- LINUS CALEB BALDWIN, 1856-1910; Series VI; 1.25' (3 boxes)
  Correspondence is arranged chronologically. Letterpress books are filed at the end of the section.
  - Correspondence
    - 1856-1886 Feb (Box 150, Folder 1-17)
    - 1886 Mar-1908 (Box 151, Folder 18-26)
    - undated (Box 151, Folder 27)
    - letterpress book, 1881-1883 (Box 151, Folder 28)
    - letterpress book, 1883-1886 (Box 152, Folder 29)
    - oversize correspondence (Box 152, Folder 30)
  - Personal Files
    - calling cards, undated (Box 152, Folder 31)
    - cattle ranches: information concerning brands, crop yields and range land, undated (Box 152, Folder 32)
    - certificate releasing LCB from military duty, 1864 (Box 152, Folder 33)
    - Iowa State Fair, Division A, LCB, Superintendent: memoranda books concerning tickets, accounts and reports, 1885 (Box 152, Folder 34)
    - juvenilia, undated (Box 152, Folder 35)
    - memorabilia, 1858, 1866, 1879, undated (Box 152, Folder 36)
    - biographical information, 1910 (Box 152, Folder 37)
- OVERSIZE, Series VII
  Consult page 117 for listing of oversize materials from Series I-VI.
  See: Oversize, box 180
- FAMILY: GENERAL, 1868-1981; Series VIII; 1' (3 boxes)
  The arrangement of this series is intended to parallel the organization of material in SERIES I of the initial donation of Beer Family Papers. As such, Correspondence, Financial Files, Personal Files, and Photographs are all arranged alphabetically by the appropriate individual or family name.
  - Correspondence
    - Baldwin family, 1868; 1886; 1890; undated (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to Baldwin family, 1941; 1962 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Elizabeth Thompson Beer, 1920-1928; 1959 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Ethelind Beer, 1976; 1980 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Gloria Beer, [ca. 1974-1976] (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, 1936 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Mary Beer, 1980-1981 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Mary and Thomas Beer, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Mary and Dorcas Beer, 1976-1977 (Box 153, Folder 9-11)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Nary G. F. Beer, 1954-1955 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Paul ("Dick") Beer, 1941-1967; undated (Box 153, Folder 13-15)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Paul ("Dick") Beer-birthday greetings and miscellanea, 1940-1956 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Paul ("Dick") Beer-will, 1973 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Richard C. Beer, 1954-1958 (Box 153, Folder 18-19)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin and Samuel H. Beer, 1967-1981 (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Beer family, 1872; 1874; 1886; 1900; 1901-1911; undated (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - Beer family-miscellaneous, 1947; undated (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - Financial Files
    - Baldwin family - deed and contract, 1885; 1900 (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) - correspondence re: Wilson-Gray notes, 1920-1922 (Box 154, Folder 24)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) - First National Bank of Yonkers, 1926-1938 (Box 154, Folder 25)
    - Beer, William C. - Fannie Edgerton (Manilla Navigation Company), 1915 (Box 154, Folder 26)
    - Beer family - deed, between Jacob and Margaret Feeter, 1899 (Box 154, Folder 27)
  - Personal Files
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin - reminiscenses of childhood, 1929 (Box 154, Folder 28)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) - D.A.R. pins; passport, 1902; 1910; 1928 (Box 154, Folder 29)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) - Fortnightly Club, 1940-1941 (Box 154, Folder 30)
    - Beer family - "Mustard and Pepper", 1895 (Box 154, Folder 31)
    - Beer family - wills, marriage certificates, miscellanea, 1886-1887; undated (Box 154, Folder 32)
  - Photographs
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin - with Calvin S. Hathaway on TV show, undated (Box 155, Folder 33)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin - in Spain, 1929; members of Neighborhood Playhouse, n.d.; with Tyler family, n.d., 1929; undated (Box 155, Folder 34)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin - Vassar College, [ca. 1910] (Box 155, Folder 35)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) - with family, undated (Box 155, Folder 36)
    - Beer, Richard and Doris, undated (Box 155, Folder 37)
    - Beer, Thomas - photographs and sketch, [ca. 1895-1940] (Box 155, Folder 38)
    - Beer family - early members, undated (Box 155, Folder 39)
    - Beer family - Nantucket property, [ca. 1910]; 1950 (Box 155, Folder 40-42)
    - Beer family - postcards, undated (Box 155, Folder 43)
    - Beer family - miscellaneous and unidentified, undated (Box 155, Folder 44-45)
    - Beer family and friends - Fisher family; Dinsmore family; Montey Woolley, undated (Box 155, Folder 46)
  - Genealogy and Biography
    - Notes on Beer family members, undated (Box 155, Folder 47)
- THOMAS BEER, 1909-1936; Series IX; 2" (1 box)
  The arrangement of this series is intended to parallel the organization of material in SERIES III of the initial donation of Beer Family Papers.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by writer.
  Published Writings is arranged chronologically under two headings:
  Saturday Evening Post and Century Magazine.
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence, 1909-1928 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Published Writings
    - Saturday Evening Post
      - "The Mighty Man", 1920 March 15 (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - "Refuge", 1920 August 28 (Box 156, Folder 3)
      - "Disastrous Joy", 1926 September 11 (Box 156, Folder 4)
      - "Midnight Blues", 1928 July 14 (Box 156, Folder 5)
      - "Life is an Art", 1929 August 10 (Box 156, Folder 6)
      - "One Never Does", 1930 January 11 (Box 156, Folder 7)
      - "Where the Heart Is", 1930 March 8 (Box 156, Folder 8)
      - "Rose Plaster", 1930 June 14 (Box 156, Folder 9)
      - "The Black Kind", 1930 October 11 (Box 156, Folder 10)
      - "International", 1930 November 29 (Box 156, Folder 11)
      - "Modesty", 1931 January 10 (Box 156, Folder 12)